What's that?
Oh, now!
Good morning, Yuki.
Sir, Clydesdale platoon is back from their recon mission to Mazurek Landing Castle.
All right, then. Let's open the well, Doc.
All units back and glad to be home.
Warrant Officer Kaiska.
Yes?
Clean up and report to the Captain's quarters. You've been requested.
Me?
That's right. It's about the Deucalion. It's headed back down here. To the Earth.
Captain, we're told to land at Port Aiden.
Please calculate optimal re-entry time in Vector and report back to me.
Yes, ma'am.
We're on the move all the time. They're trying to get as much out of us as they can. Until we're all gone.
Are you sure it's not that they just put a high value on what this ship and crew can do?
I really don't think they have any idea what to do with us. At least that's the vibe I get.
I need your approval, Captain, for the Quartermaster's supply list.
I've already checked the list over. Go ahead and send it in.
Yes, ma'am.
Attention, all hands.
We're instructed to return to Earth. At 1300 hours UTC, we will begin our re-entry sequence.
Thanks, ma'am.
We'll see you next time.
I'm falling, it's not
You can do it every single-shot
I realize it to be this power
based on the success
You can do it
My very own world
A sense of action
Feel me
Charles Teri
Son of a stage.
Calvado is quite nice.
Thank you, sir. But no, thank you.
Very well.
Tell me, will we really be escorting the Deucalion?
Temporarily, while they resupply and refit the ship.
Should be uneventful. The base they've been assigned to is close to our position.
The two of you do have some ties to that ship.
I understand you chose not to keep serving a boarder.
Being a board only opens up old wounds, so I decided not to serve on her.
I believe your younger brother is a board.
His exploits have been quite something, I hear.
Yes, sir. I guess.
May I, sir?
Certainly.
How did the other nobles react after that?
I'm told that none of them are expressing opposition openly. At least in Harklight's opinion.
Do you share that opinion, Slane?
No. They most likely won't be holding back their true feelings very much longer.
It would be in bad taste, while we're still mourning the Count.
It is an undeniable fact. Count Sosbom's death is a great loss to verse and to what we want to achieve.
I am the result of an indiscretion committed on the moon by my father, the second emperor, Gilzeria.
Father perished as a result of his second sin, Heaven's fall. That sin shattered this moon we are on.
Count Sosbom found me and offered his allegiance when I had lost my family, although I never actually knew what he was thinking deep down.
But no matter. When it comes to those who have no talent for scheming, trust becomes more difficult.
Therefore, Slane, you must weather the brunt of their envy and jealousy. Either way, you've inherited all of the Count's privileges,
as well as the special status which accrued to him as the guardian of my sister.
I am prepared for that. A duty which deserves to be envied by all.
That noble uniform. You wear it well and it suits you. But there is something you must not forget. The princess that you must protect now is here before you.
I am keenly aware of that.
To think that he named this wretched Terran as his successor, only to die immediately afterward, Count Sosbom was not blessed with good luck.
Perhaps it was just deserts for his folly. He may have been caught off guard and killed.
Are you suggesting that he was betrayed? That he was a victim of murder?
Careful. You say that without any hard evidence. It's only idle gossip.
Whatever it is, the dignity of all the knights is in the balance.
We cannot allow this Kerr to go on doing as he pleases.
Count Mazurak.
I understand that you go out of your way to avoid destructive acts of aggression because your priority is focused on seizing Earth's resources.
And no, I do not criticize you for these actions. However, now is the time to press on with the invasion of Earth immediately.
If this continues, the noble authority of the 37 clans will only decline further.
We need an alliance that will set aside differences and work together for the common good.
What are your thoughts on this, Count Mazurak?
It is a poor knight that slays any who would show him defiance.
Prove yourself superior so they won't defy you in the first place.
Wise words indeed, my lord.
Count Sosbom spoke them.
Huh?
Which is exactly why I need to make sure they remember them.
Basically, you're pretty healthy. I don't see anything particularly concerning now.
Which is what I've been telling you. So maybe it's time to take me off your patient list.
Plenty of time for that. And how's the war going?
I would have expected them to just keep coming at us without stopping.
After all, the odds of reconciliation are effectively nil now.
Mars isn't uncalculating.
Sure, some of them act purely out of hatred.
But others would rather seize the Earth and take our natural resources.
Ah, so they're restraining themselves by choice.
Here's an idea.
Hmm?
How about this? What if their attacks have diminished because they never imagined their greatest cataphracts would be taken out one after the other like dominoes?
Things haven't exactly gone according to plan for them. Maybe they're feeling a little threatened.
Let's say you're right. If so, it was one young boy who gave us the breathing space we've got.
I guess you mean Inaho.
Hmm.
I'm sure Yuki must be worried sick about him.
Yeah. She wanted him out of the military, so she kept going to the top brass.
I thought that was just a story from the rumor mill.
You know, that they finally got upset with her pestering, so they stationed her here.
Possible enemy sky carrier detected in the south.
Run! Get the station!
Hale rattle on! This is not a drill!
Listen up. We're going to hold it off here. We can't let it reach that urban area to the east. We'll wait for it to get in range. On my order, we commence attack.
Roger!
Roger that!
Attack it!
Enemy cataphract coming forward!
Our rounds are landing! Keep it going!
What the hell is that?
They're deflecting away!
Is it a tornado?
It's not that. Wind speed, air volume, and atmospheric pressure don't show any...
My hand! Feels like it's in a vice!
Watch, Count Barocruz. How I fight shows the nobility of my family title and the Orbital Knights!
Wait! Hold it! No! Clydesdale 2-2!
No! Clydesdale 2-2!
Hey! Are you okay?
Yeah, but I barely got away!
Fall back, 2-2!
What the hell have they come up with now?
Lieutenant! The gauges! Look at the levels on the accelerometer!
Gravity? Am I supposed to believe that they're able to manipulate gravity?
My readings! They're back and forth all over the whole screen! While those spheres are spinning over there around that thing, they seem to be building up an incredible amount of force that... they're using to...
Create gravity waves!
Yes!
So an object close enough is going to be torn apart by the title forces, and any attack we make is deflected, huh?
I guess so. And I imagine that the sound in our heads is a part of it.
Yeah, probably.
I do not have ill will for these Terrans, but I shall do this for the future of Verse!
Here it comes!
We can't just sit here and watch it go into the city!
We gotta draw it away somehow!
Yes, sir! But how?
Kaisuka!
Right here!
Report into the carrier!
Ask if we have any satellite bases overhead, then have the equipment to detect gravity waves!
Do you not understand how pitiful your efforts are?
It's no use! They disintegrate before they can connect!
Even if they don't cause any damage, they are keeping his attention on us!
We're another ten clicks away from the town! We're definitely drawing him farther away!
Another two kilometers south! Just another two! That's so much farther we've got to make him go!
We've got to make him go!
What's going on? Don't stop moving!
Clydesdale 2-2! Clydesdale 3-3!
We're so close!
Kaisuka!
I'll go get his attention!
You retrieve those two!
Lieutenant!
Come get me, you son of a bitch!
This is senseless. Why would you want to waste your time?
What is the point of making an effort like this?
Lieutenant...
This is not good. I am way too close.
I need to find a way to get some more distance.
A little farther.
Come on!
No!
Will I never be free of these memories?
No matter how hard I try!
Invert!
Thank you for drawing it right into position, Lieutenant.
Is that a... laser transmission?
Long time no see, Yuki.
Is that you now?
No!
Those gravity waves, they're propagating outward horizontally.
The ones that are transmitting vertically are integrated to dampen their effect.
Drift correction, 0.2 degrees per second.
Target locked.
And fire!
viet
What a lucky break that the ship we got through to was the Deucalion.
Or maybe we're just lucky that he was here.
We hit atmosphere in 10 minutes get Mustang zero zero aboard
We no longer have a line of fire to your position looks like this is all the help we can give you
No, that was plenty. Thank you young guys cut
TK six seven and six eight on designated course opening gate cleaning up this trash as a career
It's taking forever considering how huge that battle was tons of debris got scattered all around this area
It's a huge pain not easy pushing shuttles through here, sir
Radar return detected
There's no IFF signal. Sorry, sir, but we weren't able to pick it up right away. It was mixed in with signals from all of the debris
Only one unit
Why can't they get it if it's only a single unit that's because
It's ten clicks out. I can't believe it. How can it get to a dense debris field at that velocity get the catapract platoons launch now
Yuki you came back. That's great. You had us worried when you left it was like we looked up and suddenly you weren't there anymore
I'm so sorry. Just chuck it up to grown-up reasons
So now we can fight together again, right from what I hear you guys have been pretty busy. That's for sure. You seem to be doing all right
All right
Right a so tell me are you liking it here?
It's okay, I suppose
Good, I'm glad
Naho's feeling good, too
That seemed to be the case so have you seen him already? He just said hello over the radio
Well, I suppose it's possible. He really thinks that's all that's needed
All right, then so your memories surfaced again. There doesn't seem to be any way I can escape the damn things
Is it possible that perhaps they were deliberately revived huh as sort of a self-induced shock therapy you brought upon yourself to avoid losing consciousness?
No way
Lieutenant, I think it's possible. You're using those memories as a survival mechanism giving yourself a reason to fight
Of course, it's nothing you're doing consciously. Do you mean you think I won my mental war?
Hmm
At the very least I'm confident that you've won a battle. Come on now. Where'd I put it?
I really hope you can accept that much if nothing else. Huh found it. Hmm
Wait a minute now
That's where you've been hiding my bottle
If you're using your drinking to fight the demons of your past, then you're drinking takes on a whole different meaning
Hold on this glass of yours is sterile, right?
Lieutenant emergency trident base was attacked
This is a recording of the attack
They waited until the shuttles had gone into the docking bay then touched off all the munitions. They were carrying that is some seriously bad timing
No, I think that's exactly what was planned was planned
That was the base where a major battle was just fought. So it's a safe bet that supply shuttles would come
They probably checked first to make certain the reinforcements were gone
Their Intel was good. They only needed one unit
But wait the service details of munitions shuttles are supposed to be top secret
All they really do is stuff like change their registry numbers and maybe alter the supply routes
They could be sniffed out with careful crypto analysis and data sifting, but that's
No doubt they are capable of that
My Lord slain brilliantly done sir
The fiendish animal you mustn't undervalue his actions and results. He devised a plan and carried it out and did so brilliantly
We can't brand him a traitor now after this
Causes coalesce around power
The mangy Kerr has transformed himself into an alpha wolf
Now Harklyte we will return to the moon
The Tharsis slain Troyard
The thymic
I'm looking forward to the future
I'm looking for a light in the sky
I'm looking forward to the sound of the sound
I'm looking forward to the sound of the sound of the sound
Knowing that my eyes aren't happened
I'm looking forward to the sound of the sound
As first as this one I can see
Maybe if you think about this one,
than ever.
Let's jump on the mission.
Let it go in the beginning of the world.
I believe that to a start...
不要 Until getting more